TAGS- RATING <= 1200

1.Minimum Integer
http://codeforces.com/problemset/problem/1101/A

You are given q queries in the following form:

Given three integers li, ri and di, find minimum positive integer xi such that it is divisible by di and it does not belong to the segment [li,ri].

Can you answer all the queries?

Recall that a number x belongs to segment [l,r] if l≤x≤r.
Input

The first line contains one integer q
(1≤q≤500) — the number of queries.

Then q lines follow, each containing a query given in the format li ri di (1≤li≤ri≤109, 1≤di≤109). li, ri and di are integers.

Output

For each query print one integer: the answer to this query.
**********************************************************

2.The Pleasant Walk
http://codeforces.com/problemset/problem/1090/M

There are n houses along the road where Anya lives, each one is painted in one of k possible colors.

Anya likes walking along this road, but she doesn't like when two adjacent houses at the road have the same color. She wants to select a long segment of the road such that no two adjacent houses have the same color. Help Anya find the longest segment with this property.

Input

The first line contains two integers n and k — the number of houses and the number of colors (1≤n≤100000, 1≤k≤100000).

The next line contains n integers a1,a2,…,an — the colors of the houses along the road (1≤ai≤k).

Output

Output a single integer — the maximum number of houses on the road segment having no two adjacent houses of the same color.